Where?
Oh, my God. Hmm? You're making a face.
Is he coming?
Yeah, he's here.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've updated the ones you put on.
Sleep push and turn.
It's all gone.
But it hasn't flowed yet.
No, it's not.
Oh, here it comes.
It's here? I linked to it, didn't I?
Here it comes. Here it comes. It went right through.
Oh, thank you. Here it comes. Here it comes.
Here you go. It's working.
It's working. Thank God.
Thank you for waiting.
Here you go.
Today, at Kijima Kogen Park.
Yes?
It was a live performance with Tokishin-chan.
How was it? How was it?
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
I think there were some people who were really close and some who were from Kyushu,
There were so many people who came from far and wide,
Thank you very much.
There were a lot of teachers.
It was really reassuring.
Thank you very much.
Many people from the Fukuda-kai also came.
It's been a long time since I was in Kyushu,
It was great to see so many people I hadn't seen in a long time.
I was very happy. I want to come again.
Thank you very much.
I know some of you may be wondering what today's news is,
I have some very important news to share with you.
It's being prepared. I can't wait to tell you.
I know you want to say it soon.
Just a little bit more, just a little bit more.
You've been waiting for me. It's already past the hour.
Yes, it is. All of it.
I know we announced it again during the live concert, but shall we do it again?
Yes, I will. Then, let's go!
Deden!
Shachie, on June 28th, we will be releasing our 2nd EP, Awaiting Bear.
Yay!
Bear! Bear!
Yes.
Awaiting Bear.
EP of the hour.
It's been about 6 months since the EP?
It was November, right?
Yes, it has.
The long-awaited second one for Waku Waku Records.
Awaiting Bear.
The title is a little interesting,
What is it?
Kenta Matsukuma did the sound production for all the songs.
Since it was created by Matsukuma, it is called
It is Awaiting Bear!
He's wearing a bear stamp!
Wow, Bear Bear!
I like it... I'm so happy!
There are 4 songs in the album.
All the songs were written by Mr. Matsukuma.
Some of them are hot, some of them are emo, and some of them are fun.
There are also some instrumental songs on this album.
so you can practice!
There are actually 8 songs in total!
The sound is pretty good, too.
I love instrumental music. I'm glad.
I understand. Me too.
I love Mac's sound great.
I'm glad you're here, instrumentalist.
I'm looking forward to the instrumental - you're here!
This time the release format will be CD and M-card!This time, we will be releasing the product in CD and M-Card format.
This is the first time you're releasing it as an M-Card.
It's the first time.
Yes, it will be.
It's a card.
Let's change the song.
Here's the card.
I've got the power to do it.
It's the kind of thing you put on when you read it in.
It's a random selection from a total of 10 different patterns.
and the other 10 are randomly selected from 10 different patterns.
It looks good too, right?
Yes, it is.
M-card happy, he said.
You can download and listen from that card.
That's new. It's the first shirt of its kind.
I'm also excited that there are 10 different patterns. And it's random, so you never know who's going to get which one, but I love randomness.
It makes me want to collect them. I want to collect them.
The CD is 3,000 yen, and the M-card is 1,500 yen.
That's our merchandising captain. Even the price. It's better to go down to the price.
The logo is cute. This time it's with a bear, so the shirt and the bear are together.
The shirt and the bear are working together to make the strongest EP.
Let me show you the door up once?
It's close enough to see the letters.
You can buy a lot of m-cards and they're not bulky.
A lot.
CDs.
I've heard all the Tahmins say they're going to have a recession if they buy a lot of CDs.
M-card might be easier to recession-proof than CDs.
It's easier to take them home with you.
But CDs have their advantages, too.
It's great. In this day and age. Thank you. Please try to complete the collection.
I'm looking forward to working with you. And now... about cell phones...
Yes, I did, but...
I'd like to show you the new artist photo.
We're going to show you the new artist photos. We'll get to see the new clothes? That's what I'm talking about.
But these were taken just recently.
It was taken just the other day.
What was it?
What's our Asha now?
Edo eyes?
EP pink...
The apex of the previous one.
The one with the café. Like this one.
The one where they have meetings.
It's totally different.
This time I'm showing the whole group.
I'm going to show you Asha's solo work, but it's a bit of a surprise.
I'll do it this time.
Which one this time?
Which one is Ross?
What do they look like?
The cool one?
What? Can I see them one at a time? Can you slide them in?
Which one first?
Which one is better?
Okay, so the first one's the furthest away.
That's right.
Let's see your faces, one at a time.
Can I come up?
Oh, here they come.
That's it!
Leave it for me, Chii-chan.
Nice... he's teasing us.
No, you know...
Ansha's so protective of her diaper face.
He's so cute!
I don't know how close-up it is, but...
It's so cute!
It's coming from this way.
Who's this ear?
Who's got the ears?
Who are those ears?
We're not on the air yet.
We're not on air yet.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Oh, it's Mimiki!
It was like when they announced a new language.
It sure was.Indeed.
I've been teasing you more than I did the new language.
This way please!
Yes!
This angle is new.
Eh, this is interesting.
Interesting.
Cute.
Yeah.
They are all bears.
Yes, each hair style is a bear.
They are bears.
You did a bear, didn't you?
That's right.
Bear, bear arrangement... I wonder if you can see it.
I'm sure there will be pictures on twitter or something, so please take a good look at them.
The outfit is cute, too. It's very summery.
It's based on the color "Anne".
I want to wear it to a live performance.
I'd love to wear it to a concert.
Yuzuki's hair has bears in it.
Yuzuki's is on the top.
The pearls are the size of shumai.
A little bear.
Ran-chan's on the bottom.
Ni hao ku ku ah so ni hao ku ku ku
Chinese bear, Chinese bear...
Chinese bear, Chinese beer, shanshan...
Shanshan? Shanshan?
I wonder how much it's going to change.
It was a panda. Maybe it was a panda.
There's a theory going around right now.
Now it's coming out. Shanshan's theory is coming out too.
Mahon is a bear. A top bear.
What's that? From the middle.
Braids. There's a little braid sticking out.
A little Chinese.
Call me in battle.
What are you going to do?
I'm not aware of any rivalry, because I always think of Po-chan as my only rival.
I'm not conscious of anything. Just keep an eye on me.
It's like Tom and Jerry. Tom and Jerry.
Tom is in the back.
This is Jerry, and Tom is in the back.
And what?
It's like an arch with braids.
It's like a hair band.
Like a bear in a catsuit.
I've seen cat ears before.
I've never seen a bear.
It's cute.
We've all adopted bears through trial and error.
It looks like a bear.
I asked him to do it.
This is the artist's photo.
Please spread the word!
The quality of the image is down right now.
The signal is bad, so it's a little off.
You can see it later.
You'll be able to see it later.
Go on.
Okay.
May I go?
Sure.
Here's the next bit of information.
What's up?
It's a free live concert tour!
Yay!
For quite a while now.
I think the information that we are going to have a free live concert has already been announced.
And the free live show is...
Chachi and Kuma's Relash
Rilash!
Chachi and Kuma's Crush is a thrill to behave!
It's going to be held!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
You don't say!
Crush the bear and Crush the bear and you've become a rilakkuma!
Oh, my God!
You don't know what I'm talking about.You don't know what I'm talking about.
It's not Rilash.
Rilakkuma dumped me.
Crash.
It's amazing.
You can see Rilakkuma from the back.
It's really Rilakkuma!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Team Chachi Free Live Tour 2023 Spring/Summer
Accelerating Excitement with Chachi and Bear Crash
Coming soon!
Yay!
It's also the date for Chachi-sama.
I'm sure there are a lot of you who were wondering what kind of free live show it would be.
We are happy to announce that we are going to release our second EP
We will be playing songs from the EP and so on.
That's the kind of information we have for you.
Here are the details.
I'll give you the details.
Let's start with the details. May 6th, HMV soccer event, this is only a benefit event.
May 7th is at AEON MALL Nagoya Noritake Garden.
This stage is not the usual place where you sing and dance on a stage.
This is a live concert with a slightly different atmosphere because there is no stage.
So it's a different kind of atmosphere.
It's a Mezura, a Mezura!
Rare!
Mezura live on May 7th.
Sunday, May 13th, Saturday at Laraport Tatsuhiko Tatsuhiko Ryukawa
Sunday, May 14, Tokyo, Raraport Toyoshu
I'm sorry, I know you can't see the words.
I know you can't see the words, but it's in those spring words.
I'll tweet this again later with just my voice, but I hope you can see it.
I'll tweet this again later, but I hope you can see it.
Saturday, May 27, Aichi Prime Tree Red Series
Sunday, May 28th at Morinomiya Cuse Mall in Osaka
Sunday, May 28th
Oh, I think we have the same day in the schedule.
Sorry, it's June 4th, Sunday at Tower Records Shibuya in Tokyo.
Then Saturday, June 10th, there's Shizuoka.
Oh, yes!
Raraport Iwata.
Next, on Sunday, June 11th, we have Aichi AEON MALL Otaka.
Saturday, June 24th at AEON MALL Makuhari-Shintoshin, Chiba
Then on Sunday, June 25th, Tokyo Kameido Clock.
And on Wednesday, June 28th, at Tower Records Kintetsu Paste in Aichi, Japan.
Paste
Yay!
Bye!
There are a lot of transparent editions, so...
There will be another one on the 12th, a little over two weeks ago.
There are some places where you can speak up, and some places where you can't.
We'll be sharing them on the official website as they happen.
Please check it out!
Talk session, photo session, etc.
Privilege meeting
I'm sure there are a lot of people who would like to talk to you since you're a Japanese actor.
We feel the same way, so please come!
The rules are getting softer and softer.
So please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
And, we're going to have another free concert tour.
Stamp Rally
We're going to hold a celebration.
Everyone loves stamp rally. Stamp rally.
Chororo, is this Vogue continuing the stamp rally? And so on.
That's great.
Talk about stamp rally.
So I guess it's a new stamp rally.
At the last free live,
We had done it at the time of the App Live, but this time we're doing a new version of the stamp rally, the "waiting bear" version, or is that what it's called?
The stamp rally paper has been renewed, and the benefits have also been renewed, so please participate in the stamp rally at many places.
What if you came to all of them?
All of them?
There are already up to 10, so one of them should be filled.
That's right. For 3 points, you get a Waku Waku Records logo sticker, for 6 points, you get an Asha sticker, and for 10 points, you get a Killer Whale ticket.
Wow, that's great.
But there are 12 of them, so I hope you'll come more often.
There are 12.
If you come to almost all of them, you will get one ticket.
So, by all means, please come.So, please come and join us!
Please join our stamp rally and get our special offers.
And get our memories, too!
I've got a question.
Can I use the stamps I've used so far?
Yes, you can.
So, please continue with the old one.
And when you have 10, you can get a new metabolic rate.
I see.
Do you have a stamp rally every time you buy a ticket?
Almost.
Then I'd better bring it with me.
Regardless of this for Rims.
Second 2 metabolism.
I guess you could call it a second metabolism.
Yes, that's right.
So if you've had it before...
please bring it.
If you're a debutante who joined us from here
Please get a new one!
If you are using the previous one as much as possible
If you can save up your old one before going to the new one
I think it's environmentally friendly.
That's for sure.
I'd like to see it.
And we'll take good care of them one by one.
I don't have one of those. Like a tufmino.
Not yet.
And yet...
Super or stroke energy.
You've got an exciting mind.
I've been doing this a hundred times my whole life.
I'm not even going to finish.
I've had bad energies.
It's been too long.
It means the same thing.
Well, that's a lot of fun, isn't it?
You said pretty much everything you wanted to say.
I did.
I wanted to say it.
I wanted to tell you, that's why I asked this question.
It's just 7:00 p.m., seven minutes before the show.
Seven minutes ago, I was on the air, and I saw a lot of different media.
I don't know if it's up yet.
If it goes up.
I think it's time to go.
When it goes up, I get retweets and likes.
Like it
Please spread the word!
I'm a little late for the start.
That's right.
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
I've given out a lot of information.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who haven't been able to sort through it.
Please check it out!
Please save the answers!
Thank you so much!
Where do you want this set up? I'd like to see everyone's
Header
Header?
I don't know if it's gonna fit.
I think we can get the faces in there.
I think it'll fit.
Here.
Twitter.
Okay, guys, here's the header for Twitter.
If it's this header, it's got a lot of pull.
Mm-hmm. That's for sure.
Everyone has a pull.
I don't think I've ever seen a header with four people's faces in this close-up before.
Hey.
See you later,
There it is.
Everyone, wear a bear.
Please take care of them.Best regards.
Is this area about free live?
Yes, I would like to know more about the free live concert. Yes, we do.
Then there are other live concerts.
There are other free live tours, of course,
We also perform at various festivals,
And of course, on July 9, we will be celebrating my birthday,
My birthday party and the member-produced performance "Shachi,
Diner Killer Whale.
Yay!
I'm currently in the second round of the FC selection process, and it ends today.
Is that so? We have to hurry.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up. Mizuki's Birthday Festival.
Yes, for the birthday festival.
The header is perfect. It's so perfect.
Definitely make it a header.
It's good. That's good.
Let's go on patrol. Let's all do it together.
Let's do low-mobbers, do patrols, do low-mobbers.
I think there are a lot of people who do low-mobbers.
Vertically and horizontally, vertically and vertically. Cell phones too.
Vertically, horizontally, vertically, and vertically.
I was wondering why.
Everyone was laying their phones down during dinner.
All of us. You know what I mean.
I was wondering what hashtag would be good.
This is the second EP.
But it's kind of hard to use lower case letters.
If I give it a shot, will you give it to me?
Various kinds of hashtags? Second EP
Oh, right, like three.
Think about a representative one first.
One? Oh, you mean like that.
Waiting Bear... you put it in katakana.
That's easy.
But why not English too?
But here, it opens up.
Then it's hard to read.
I see...
But that's what Mr. Matsuguma meant. I'd like to keep it that way.
Last time it was "shachibu choppa", "inpibu choppa"...
Shachi Matsuguma
Shachi Matsuguma Shachi Matsuguma
Easy to understand, easy to understand
Shachi Matsukuma Matsukuma is the kanji for Matsukuma
I'll write it on the back of this one.
Pen, pen, pen...
Oh, yes... can I have the bear too?
If you can afford it, please make a copy of the waiting bear and write it in English.
Yes, sir.
A single line?
It's drawn in a strange way.
White?
Blue.
Blue is good.
Okay, you want to do this one?
This one.
Done.
This must be easy to understand.
It's easy to understand.
Please have them put this on and look at it.
Mr. Matsuguma can do the English sample.
You'll get it, too, Mr. Matsukuma. You'll get it.
And, "Awaiting Bear", this one in romaji, this one in katakana...
Please make your own original and put it on it!
Thank you very much!
There will be many live concerts from here on.
I'm sure you will have a lot of opportunities to see each other until Chachi Summer.
I'm sure we will have many opportunities to meet each other until Chachi Summer. The 4th of May is the fan's music face during this Golden Week.
Yokohama for sure.
I'm looking forward to it because the demographic is different from other idols recently.
And the dieting group, too.
You were sandwiched in between.
And the next day, the 5th of May, is Japan Central Idol Fest.
This is right next to Centralia.
Sky Expo.
It's gone global.
Are you curious?
Sky Expo.
Look.See.
I am too happy.
So everyone, please don't go in.
Please watch a lot.
So we will give you a stage for each of you.
No matter what kind of live performance.
You're looking forward to it.
Please enjoy.
I'm looking forward to it.
First of all, you must retweet the release information when it comes out,
Apply for the second round of FC on July 9 is a must and do it immediately.
It's heavy, heavy.
I have to do it.
You must do it.
It's a MUST, please.
Please do it.
Well then, I guess that's all the news from us.
How was it?
Suddenly.
Covering.
At the new training park.
We covered Gyutto.
We also collaborated on skiing.
We also did an anthem together.
Tokishin-chan did Triple Seven.
Hou-chan was there as MC, but I think he was the furthest away from us in the staff.
Tokishin-chan was the one who was the most distant from us in the staff.
Tokishin-chan is a cute girl.
I could see that this was going to happen during the live performance.
It was a lot of fun.
I think it was a lot of fun.
It was fresh.
It was fresh and she was so cute.
Thank you so much.
I was so excited.
You were so cute the whole time.
I felt like, all of the perks today were in this pose.
They were all squeezing each other.
The chairman of the board of directors is putting it on gettok.
We're all squished together.
You can see it on TikTok.
If you couldn't make it, just show us a little bit.
Just a little.
No, you can't. Everyone, watch it on TikTok.
That's right.
Later on, when I'm done with this YouTube.
That's a good idea. Then I'll add it to the mast.
Added.
And then we have LowMova.
So many.
There's a lot.
So much low-moba talk.
Put up a barrier.
Wait a minute, I'm not putting up a barrier on this particular day.
We only have 20 hours during the show.
It's not safe. I'm really going to tighten it up.
That's right. So, it's a roadmobile during the concert.
It's during the Roadmobile event,
For those of you who have joined us,
our team and save power together.
I hope you all will do the same.
We will enjoy it to the fullest. We will have a lot of fun after this.
So we'll have dinner afterwards, right?
Yes! Let's eat!
Wow! We can finally eat! I'm so happy!
I'm going to eat triten!
I'm so hungry.
I'm already hungry.
Well then, thank you all for coming today.
Thank you very much!
Well then, we're going to have a free live performance from here on out,
Let's all get excited!
Please do so!
That's all for now, Yatteho-San.
That's all for now, Hou-san. That's all for now,
That's all for now.
Bye bye!